{
"question": "上げる",
"answer": "あげる"
},
{
"question": "結婚",
"answer": "けっこん"
},
{
"question": "言葉",
"answer": "ことば"
},
{
"question": "目",
"answer": "め"
},
{
"question": "走る",
"answer": "はしる"
},
{
"question": "名前",
"answer": "なまえ"
},
{
"question": "旅行",
"answer": "りょこう"
},
{
"question": "道",
"answer": "みち"
},
{
"question": "飛行機",
"answer": "ひこうき"
},
{
"question": "映画",
"answer": "えいが"
},
{
"question": "音楽",
"answer": "おんがく"
},
{
"question": "木",
"answer": "き"
},
{
"question": "大学",
"answer": "だいがく"
},
{
"question": "時計",
"answer": "とけい"
},
{
"question": "家族",
"answer": "かぞく"
},
{
"question": "花",
"answer": "はな"
},
{
"question": "猫",
"answer": "ねこ"
},
{
"question": "毎日",
"answer": "まいにち"
},
{
"question": "宿題",
"answer": "しゅくだい"
},
{
"question": "雪",
"answer": "ゆき"
},
